[{"answer": "Well, what we see, Piers, is the army is fully deployed in the streets of Cairo.", "docId": "110128pmt", "aSentId": 21, "question": "What is going on right now?", "qSentId": 20}, {"answer": "Well, in the next few days, we'll see.", "docId": "110128pmt", "aSentId": 33, "question": "Are the protesters right to see the army as the saviors, or could they possibly be misled here?", "qSentId": 32}, {"answer": "People want change.", "docId": "110128pmt", "aSentId": 46, "question": "In very simple terms, what do you think this protest is really about?", "qSentId": 45}, {"answer": "It sounded like a lead balloon.", "docId": "110128pmt", "aSentId": 61, "question": "How did his speech go down on the ground?", "qSentId": 60}, {"answer": "The key message to President Mubarak, Piers, was not good enough.", "docId": "110128pmt", "aSentId": 110, "question": "When you watched President Obama's speech this evening, reading between all the lines, and it was very carefully phrased, what do you thing the key messages were that were going back to President Mubarak?", "qSentId": 109}, {"answer": "It could get a whole lot worse, piers.", "docId": "110128pmt", "aSentId": 133, "question": "I mean, how bad could this get, and what are the implications not just for America, but for the world?", "qSentId": 132}, {"answer": "Well, the administration served notice today and voices from Congress are serving even tougher notice.", "docId": "110128pmt", "aSentId": 155, "question": "How do we get rid of a guy if he doesn't want to leave?", "qSentId": 154}, {"answer": "John, Wolf, thank you so much for that.", "docId": "110128pmt", "aSentId": 169, "question": "And the key question is: what does President Mubarak do in the next 48 hours and how does the Egyptian army react if he refuses to yield power and the demonstrators stay on the streets?", "qSentId": 168}, {"answer": "I think it will take some time.", "docId": "110128pmt", "aSentId": 188, "question": "Where do you think this is going to end, Amir?", "qSentId": 187}, {"answer": "I can simply -- I can easily say the majority sympathize with the protesters even though they haven't participated.", "docId": "110128pmt", "aSentId": 196, "question": "Have you got any way of working that out?", "qSentId": 195}, {"answer": "I think this falls into the category of delusional.", "docId": "110128pmt", "aSentId": 219, "question": "What's going to happen here, do you think?", "qSentId": 218}, {"answer": "I think, to start it is.", "docId": "110128pmt", "aSentId": 229, "question": "Is that, you think, the reality?", "qSentId": 228}, {"answer": "Well, I think the slow developing situation, even the incidents that have marked this year, the explosion at promise in Alexandria, the beating and killing of a businessman earlier, all these were events that signaled that on top of the disconnect, trouble was brewing.", "docId": "110128pmt", "aSentId": 250, "question": "So, it's not much of a surprise, is it really?", "qSentId": 249}, {"answer": "Well, I think the real history of American engagement in Egypt begins with Camp David and the Egyptian-Israeli peace agreement that was reached, and has helped preserve the peace in the middle east between Egypt and Israel.", "docId": "110128pmt", "aSentId": 261, "question": "Or is it beginning to look like it's backfiring?", "qSentId": 260}, {"answer": "Piers, absolutely.", "docId": "110128pmt", "aSentId": 273, "question": "Is that your reading of this?", "qSentId": 272}, {"answer": "Oh, I think -- I think it will be very quick, because, of course, he's relying right now -- he's pulled the police back.", "docId": "110128pmt", "aSentId": 285, "question": "If the aid does get shut down, how long could Mubarak continue in office, do you think?", "qSentId": 284}, {"answer": "We're certainly seeing something that's very historic.", "docId": "110128pmt", "aSentId": 308, "question": "What are the global repercussions of what we're witnessing in Egypt tonight?", "qSentId": 307}, {"answer": "Not necessarily.", "docId": "110128pmt", "aSentId": 323, "question": "With what is going on and the turmoil that we're witnessing, is the peace treaty with Israel going to be a casualty here?", "qSentId": 322}, {"answer": "Well, globally and specifically to the Arab world, I think they are very disappointed with the American language, especially Vice President Biden's language.", "docId": "110128pmt", "aSentId": 336, "question": "What's been the impact, do you think, of Vice President Biden's statement globally, and specifically to the Arab world?", "qSentId": 335}, {"answer": "I -- well, it may support him.", "docId": "110128pmt", "aSentId": 348, "question": "Do you think the Obama administration would support him?", "qSentId": 347}, {"answer": "We've seen similar use of these sites in Iran and also in China.", "docId": "110128pmt", "aSentId": 391, "question": "Piers?", "qSentId": 390}, {"answer": "Well, what happened in Egypt today, in the last 24 hours, seems to be unprecedented in the history of the Internet, the fact that basically all service providers were shut down.", "docId": "110128pmt", "aSentId": 395, "question": "Or are there always ways around this now?", "qSentId": 394}, {"answer": "Not right now, because I think they have a lot to handle to worry about single reporters or single organizations.", "docId": "110128pmt", "aSentId": 434, "question": "Are you worried about that?", "qSentId": 433}, {"answer": "I think the police have always been violent, but we haven't seen it this way, and especially because we haven't seen this many people on the street at the same time.", "docId": "110128pmt", "aSentId": 452, "question": "What are you making of what you're seeing on the ground here?", "qSentId": 451}]